{
    "responses": [
        {
            "question": "hello",
            "response": "hi",
            "probability": "43.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thank you ",
            "response": "your welcome",
            "probability": "43.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "hello",
            "response": "Hi there, how can I help?",
            "probability": "0.99999976"
        },
        {
            "question": "felling bad today",
            "response": "Come Come elucidate your thoughts",
            "probability": "0.7513679"
        },
        {
            "question": "everything looks black ",
            "response": "Come Come elucidate your thoughts",
            "probability": "0.6683883"
        },
        {
            "question": "want to die",
            "response": "I'm very sorry to hear that but you have so much to look forward to. Please seek help by contacting: 9152987821.",
            "probability": "0.96976435"
        },
        {
            "question": "where can I get help",
            "response": "Feeling comfortable with the professional you or your child is working with is critical to the success of the treatment. Finding the professional who best fits your needs may require research. Start by searching for providers in your area.",
            "probability": "0.47505137"
        },
        {
            "question": "ss",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "df",
            "response": "Oh okay. Why don't you tell me more about it?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "hello",
            "response": "Good to see you again",
            "probability": "0.99999976"
        },
        {
            "question": "afds",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "d",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "ss",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "xcc",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "kk",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "ddd",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "fsd",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "jl",
            "response": "Tell me more about it.",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "fasd",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "s",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "sd",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "cd",
            "response": "I'm listening. Tell me more.",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "asdf",
            "response": "Oh okay. Why don't you tell me more about it?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "asdf",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "df",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "sdf",
            "response": "Oh I see. Tell me more",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "afas",
            "response": "I'm listening. Tell me more.",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "asf",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "s",
            "response": "I'm listening. Tell me more.",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "dsfs",
            "response": "Oh okay. Why don't you tell me more about it?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "ddd",
            "response": "I'm listening. Tell me more.",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "sdfas",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "fsd",
            "response": "Oh okay. Why don't you tell me more about it?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "ds",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "fds",
            "response": "I see. What else?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "fsd",
            "response": "Oh okay. Why don't you tell me more about it?",
            "probability": "0.36399156"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hi",
            "response": "Good to see you again",
            "probability": "0.99999833"
        },
        {
            "question": "what is schizophrenia",
            "response": "Schizophrenia is a complex mental illness that affects how a person thinks, feels, behaves, and relates to others. The illness occurs in both men and women, but it is slightly more common in men. The first episode typically occurs in the late teens to early twenties\u2014usually earlier for men than for women. People can also develop the illness later in life. As many as one person out of 100 may experience schizophrenia.",
            "probability": "0.994249"
        },
        {
            "question": "hi",
            "response": "Good to see you again",
            "probability": "0.99999833"
        },
        {
            "question": "hi",
            "response": "Good to see you again",
            "probability": "0.99999833"
        },
        {
            "question": "hi",
            "response": "Good to see you again",
            "probability": "0.99999833"
        }
    ]
}